https://beautybond.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Beauty Bond Privacy Policy.
With personalized products, services and offers
We respect your privacy and choices. You can opt-out at any time.
We do not sell your data
We require partners to abide by the law and protect your information
We will continue to evolve and update our privacy and security practices because retaining your trust is important to us
Our detailed privacy policy below describes the types of information we collect from you directly, from your interactions with us (on our sites, mobile apps, digital tools (collectively, “Sites”) and advertising), how we use it, how we protect it, and your rights as our consumer.This policy is for consumers and visitors of our Sites in the United States only. If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us.
This privacy policy does not cover information that you submit on third party websites, apps, social platforms (“Platforms”) even if we communicate with you on those sites. For example, if you post something on Facebook, Twitter or You Tube, that information is governed by the privacy policies on those Platforms.
BELOW IS OUR PRIVACY POLICY AND PLEASE CONTACT US IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS.
HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION
Beauty Bond collects information that you provide to us, from your engagement with our brand sites and platforms, advertising, media, and from third parties who have your consent to share it.
WHY WE USE DATA
Everything we do, and the data we collect, is in pursuit of bringing beauty experiences to your life
We use data to communicate with you about our beauty products, services, answer questions and create better experiences.  We use data for tailored advertising and communications.
We may combine information that we collect via one method (e.g., from a website, our digital advertising) with another method (e.g., an offline event). We do this to get a more complete view of your preferences for our beauty products and services, which, in turn, allows us to serve you better and with more customization and better beauty products.
HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION
We share information with the third parties (vendors, agencies and businesses) that help us run our sites, our business, and retail our products to further Beauty Bond beauty mission. We do not sell your data or permit re-use of personal information for independent use without your consent. We share information to the extent we need to prevent fraud, when required by law or authorities and in the event of a sale of our company.
YOUR CHOICES
You can unsubscribe from our sites at any time.  You can also opt-out of interest based advertising as well as SMS messaging, push notifications.
*************************************************************************************************************
DETAILED PRIVACY POLICY
How We Collect Information (USA)
Beauty Bond collects information that you provide to us, information from your engagement with our Sites, advertising and media, and information from third parties who have gained your consent to share it. We may combine information that we collect via one method (e.g., from a website, digital advertising engagement) with another method (e.g., an offline event).  We do this to get a more complete view of preferences for our beauty products and services, which, in turn, allows us to serve you better and with more customization and better beauty products.
Please contact us if you have any questions.
×
OK
×
